biofuelsdigest.com 2014-06-26

# Privacy : Biofuels Digest

Privacy  
Ascension Publishing Inc. (“AP”) collects and uses the personal information that you submit online as described herein. AP reserves the right to modify the terms of this policy at any time. Such modifications shall become effective immediately upon posting. Your continued use of, or registration with, AP shall constitute your acceptance of these terms. If you do not agree to the terms of this policy, in whole or in part, you are not authorized to use the website and should terminate registration by following the opt-out instructions.

Collection of Information  
AP only collects personal information which you provide in response to specific information requests on biofuelsdigest.com, biomassdigest.com or geothermaldigest.com. This information may include, among other things, name, address, phone number and email address. In addition, we may collect your IP address and other information through the use of electronic “cookies.”

Use of Information  
By registering with AP, you consent to the collection, processing, and transfer of your personal information in accordance with this policy. AP may use your information: (1) for the purpose for which it was collected, as disclosed at the time such information is provided to us; (2) to protect the rights or property of AP and other registrants of AP websites, and (3) as required by federal, state or local law. We may also share your personal information with our trusted partners, advertisers, service providers, affiliates, and other third parties that we believe can provide you with information or support related to your initial online inquiry or with additional special offers and opportunities. AP screens the third parties with whom it shares personal information but makes no guarantee about their use and protection of your personal information or their willingness or ability to abide by our privacy policy. Also, AP is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of any websites to which AP links.

Security  
AP regularly monitors its website and databases for fraud, abuse, and unauthorized use of information to protect your personal information that is under our control.

Do Not Call Registry Compliance  
By submitting personal contact and/or financial information to AP through its website, you hereby grant written permission to AP and its business partners to contact you by telephone, mail, and/or e-mail. Further, by registering with AP through this website you are consenting to receive phone calls from AP and its business partners and thereby registrants waive their right to file a claim with the FTC or any other agency in reference to these calls or contacts.

Opt-Out Opportunity  
AP registrants may opt-out of receiving further communications from AP at any time by following the “unsubscribe” instructions in any AP e-mail received by registrant. Please note that unsubscribing from one email list does not automatically unsubscribe you from any other email list that you may be on. Please read the email carefully to find out which list you are unsubscribing from.

Assignment  
In its sole discretion, AP may transfer, sell or assign your personal information collected on and through this website to one or more third parties, as a result of the sale, merger, consolidation, change in control, transfer of substantial assets, reorganization or liquidation of AP.
